Thank you for watching
Class B Specialties Presentation
High, high, high!
The members come up with their own B-class special skills and present them all at once!
Bananaman will judge whether or not they can be used in the future.
Tonight, too, please watch with a low hurdle!
Next is Mukai's teary onion cutting!
Like this
Here you go.
It's a tear-jerker, right?
Yes.
Be careful with that.
Chopped.
I'm scared.
Oh, you're so close.
I don't cry when I'm that close.
Oh, my God.
I do that a lot.
Why are you okay?
You don't even blink.
That's the scarier part of the story.
I'm getting scared.
I mean, I'm not crying.
You're not crying. That's great, that's great, that's great.
I'm not crying.
I'm not vomiting.
That's great!
Let's go! Next is Yoda.
I'm Yoda. I'm going to do an animal imitation.
Here you go.
It's kind of B-grade.
I'll do a voice imitation of a siamang.
Go ahead.
This is terrible.
You did it, didn't you?
Come on, Mukai.
What should I do with that?
I mean, really... isn't it still too much to ask for?
Are you holding back? Or do you really feel nothing?
I don't feel anything.
That's why I put my face so close to it, but it doesn't come out.
This is amazing.
What's the verdict on Mukai's grade B skill?
Maybe it's great, but he needs to do more or he'll get hurt. I'm with you.
I agree with you completely.
I don't want people to think that.
the newest animal impersonator is the bag-tailed long-eared monkey.
I've heard that voice before... a real fan who can do it now.
I've heard that voice before.
I know you did this.
I bet you did this.
That's all you need to do, Tomo.
No, I just need to get started.
Yeah, it's funny.
Yoda's doing it here.
Yoda's sack-armed long monkey...
Oh, yeah!
This is definitely a growing animal series, so yes, what else can we do? Well, maybe we could show off the dog...
Oh, yeah.
It's Yoda now, right?
Yoda's about to throw up.
What was that?
It was a chicken.
I had a bit of a live throat infection.
I'll be fine.
Good morning. - Morning.
What's that?
It's Yoda.
I love Yoda's.
Good morning, Yoda.
Yoda's about to throw up.
I can't get it right.
Maybe it's good that Yoda's doing it.
It might be good.
Let's continue.
I'm Tamura.
Bangs that never fall out.
Here you go.
Bangs of bangs.
Wow!
Oh, my God. Oh, my God.
Oh, wow.
Live and live wind
Oh, my God.
You don't have to move. I'm not moving.
My hair is so smooth.
That's great.
Now, let's continue with the rock-paper-scissors game where one hand always wins.
When the right hand wins, the right hand is stronger.
Right hand wins all the time.
Surprisingly, I can't do it.
I can't do it. I can't do it.
It's an imitation of Matsuo Emonji's face.
The crowd went wild.
It's good, isn't it?
Let's continue... with the 15th Tokugawa Shogun, Sakaguchi.
I'm already insured through the nose.
The way he screams... it's amazing.
Here we go!
One up.
You were wrong on the way.
You're wrong!
It's not the same on the way.
It's a song to memorize.
Here you go.
Kitamura.
Amazing... with the spray.
Idol girls often fix their hair.
There are girls who fix their bangs after the opening of a live show.
But I don't fix my bangs once during the show.
I don't touch my bangs even once.
Everyone says that's great, but don't you guys do that too?
I'm jealous.
You can do that, can't you?
Just spray it on.
Mao was in another dimension. When it was raining at Jingu, everyone was falling apart, but Mao was the only one who survived.
Even in the rain?
Yes, he had bangs in the rain.
Wow, that's amazing, not just anyone can do that.
Yeah, I thought it was everyone, so I was wondering what it was.
How did you judge Kagura's bangs?
Oh!
That's what everyone says.
I'm glad.
You're really good at rock-paper-scissors-paper.
I can't do it when I'm surprised
That's right.
I was taking dance lessons, and there was a lesson where we were supposed to do this while doing the dance steps.
I had a lesson where I was supposed to do this while doing the dance steps.
It's too fast for you to see, but I really won.
The right one won?
Yes.
But you can do it on the left.
That's great.
I won on the right.
Oh, my God, I'm winning all the time.
What about left?
He never loses.
That's great.
It's hard to tell.
I've been practicing really hard all day.
Are you good at that, too?
Triangle here, triangle there.
I can do that.
That's great.
You're good at that.
Yes, I'm sure.
What's Ogawa's grade B rock-paper-scissors?
Go ahead.
Oh, man!
This is good.
I thought if this didn't work, I'd be finished.
Well... the kids you told me about today... I have to throw them out.
There were a lot of kids I had to throw away.
Matsuo.
Yes, Matsuo.
Imitating emoticons.
Like this one.
No, it's fine.
Here.
You're crazy, aren't you?
It's cute. It's cute.
It's like a Mytz character.
The corners of his mouth drop a lot.
No one else can do that.
So cute!
You're right, it's hard to do.
Can't you do anything other than this face?
Can you do anything but this face?
What?
Like the one with the...
Do you get it?
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Shall we go?
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Well...
It's okay. I'll just take it off.
Then Tokugawa 15, I made a mistake, didn't I say "family" twice?
I'm confident I can make it to the 8th.
There's a song I can say before going to bed.
I can say it if I'm on a roll. That's the point.
If you say it after a Coke or something, it's permanent.
Sakaguchi's judgment on Junmemoro-no-Sakaguchi's special skills is...
Well, well, well, well...
It's good. This will appeal to a wide range of people.
Yes! I'm kind of hoping he fails a little bit.
When you say it with this title...
It's a B-movie.
Then I won't practice.
I fail a lot.
I don't think you should ever be efficient.
Now, now, here's where things change a little bit.
Mr. Himura, please.
Let's have the battle to determine the No. 1 skill in Nogizaka!
In this survey, there were several members who had the same special skills.
So I'd like to announce the No. 1 member of Nogizaka with the same skill.
All right, let's see.
Let's start with the one who wrote "kendama.
I see.
So, from now on, when we decide on the number one, that person will be the one with kendama.
Kendama.
We'll decide who is the best kendama player in Nogizaka.
I see.
3 of them will participate in Kendama Summit Battle.
These 3 might be able to do it.
They are saying that
In short, how do you feel confident?
I'm confident... it depends on my luck or on the day.
When I am good, I can do it.
That's the pattern.
If it's good, I can do it.
What do you think?
I've actually done one release on this show.
I released it once in this program.
Relay? During the chair relay.
I've been successful with Kendama.
I changed it up.
It's a little too much applause.
It's not enough.
I'd like to get this one, too.
Cheerful
I only started this year.
This year?
What? So you've only been doing it for about three months?
What made you start playing?
My kendama.
Really?
What made you start?
That's so stylish.
I bought it purple because I thought of Nogizaka.
Well, I'd like to win, wouldn't you?
Yes, I do.
If there's someone who can do better than that...
If there's someone who can do something amazing, like traveling around the world...
He's done it.
What? You can do that?
What can he do?
He can play kamekens and go around the world.
He can play yakyuken.
No, that's her.
Kendama.
We don't need this tournament anymore.
She's the clear choice.
I didn't tell you because she's A level.
She's an A level.
Can you do it forever?
I can do it.
You're definitely in first place.
So...
And this time...
I'm in ninth place.
So we're in ninth place this time, too.
Sudden entry
Four players also held a frown endurance battle.
We've got a bad guy in here.
Suddenly, a leisure class came in.
But if I drop out early, I won't be able to claim my name this time
Oh, no!
So you're in.
I'm in.
I'm shaking.
So if you drop out early, you can't tell us even if you can do something amazing.
This is suddenly very tense.
Let's see who's the Nogizaka kendama champion!
Here we go!
I'm sure he'll do it.
What's this?
Okay, here we go! Moshi moshi camera!
If you miss, it's over. We're done.
It's over. I'm Mukai.
It's over. I'm Mukai. It's over too soon.
What are you trying to say? Maybe I was nervous.
Maybe I was nervous. I'm sure I can do it.
Why did you do it on your own?
I felt like I wasn't strong enough. Okay, Mukai, you're in first place.
Let's decide who comes in second.
Let's see who will be the No. 2 kendama player in Nogizaka.
Hello, turtles!
Of all the turtles in the world, none walks as fast as you.
I've decided. It's over.
Why did you take so long?
No, it's over. Legend has it.
Why did you start playing Kendama this year?
I was so impressed with your skills that I bought one.
I see... because it's so big, I can't do any tricks with it.
I can't do it. Sorry, I made a mistake.
I'm sorry, it's not a thrust.
I can't do it, I can't do it, I can't do it.
The tip of the sword...
I can do it!
I'll give it one shot. I'll try my best.
Spinning and bouncing the tip of the sword...
Spinning makes it easier to get it in, centrifugal force makes it easier to get it in.
It'll be great if you can do it in one shot!
Oh, wow...
That's the way to do it.
Wait a minute... why are you doing this to yourself?
I haven't seen it yet. I'm not looking at it right now.
Please don't do that.
Let's give it a shot.
Let's turn it.
If you turn it, it'll go in.
Reply by force.
Oh, wow!
That's great!
You did it! Mukai, can you show us your technique?
It's yakyuken.
What's "yakyuken"?
Fly him over here and let him ride.
Hit it like a baseball.
Come back here again.
And at the end, you take off your clothes, right?
Not that way.
Not that way?
Yakyuken.
Let's have him do it.
I can do it.
Let's get you undressed before we do it.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Mukai is good at kendama.
But that's what I meant.
Please don't do that to the other two.
Please show me when you practice and get good at it.
Next, seven of you entered without blinking an eye.
Are you confident?
Yes, I can do it in 4 minutes.
Really?
Nice!
Keiko Yoda did it for 4 minutes, right?
On Thanksgiving.
She did!
Are you sure, Lilia?
We had a showdown on the show before.
I won.
I think I can do it.
I'm just going to have to be patient.
Okay.
Come on, Yoda.
Well...
I've decided not to do it.
What?
What's wrong?
You're scaring me, Rei.
She's serious now, Makoto.
But there's a chance that it will close unexpectedly under the right conditions.
I think there are times when you go early.
The sweatiest hands of the year
The sweatiest hands of the year!
That's great, Makoto, I really don't want to lose this kind of thing.
That's what I'm talking about, Seimi.
I love it!
Go for it, don't ever lose!
I don't know, but she looks really strong.
No, she looks strong.
She does look strong.
You know, actresses, when they do these shoots...
If you blink at the start of a shoot...
That's the kind of training they do naturally.
I see.
That's why actresses are surprisingly good at it.
Are you confident about it?
I've done it before and was able to do it for a few minutes.
I think I can do it.
There's a lot of pollen today.
It's sunny.
Yes, it is.
It's a crazy party right now.
It's a good tournament, isn't it?
It's a great competition.
Okay, well, the judges...
Can I have the judges watch for a moment?
Just watch them for a second.
Now, if you blink, you can raise your hand.
Yes, ma'am.
The road to becoming a great actress.
Who will be the first to blink?
Let's go!
Let's start!
Here we go.
Well, this is it. The winner will get a few minutes.
Oh, it's over. So fast.
I don't know. It's fast.
But that's how it goes sometimes.
Matsuo retired after 7 seconds, Ikeda dropped out after 40 seconds.
One minute elapsed for the remaining five.
This is what they all look like, right?
In this competition, it's all about the face.
The afterthought is moving.
Ogawa's in trouble, too.
Ogawa's a little stiff, too.
1:30, it's getting tough, isn't it?
Her eyes are starting to show.
Oh, Seimyah!
Seimyah's done!
Gatsulak, please squat.
I just did it for a second.
Yoda's done!
Three to go.
Great!
Kubo, Lilia, and Ogawa.
Ogawa's alive!
Oh, Lilia!
Foot!
Kubo, keep going!
Go, Kubo!
Kubo strong!
Kubo's eyes are very interesting?
But Kubo win!
Kubo win!
What's the record?
925!
Well, well, well.
Seimyan's crying like a baby!
Smile
It's true.
I'm crying so hard.
It's closed.
It's closed, isn't it?
It's so frustrating.
Losing to Mr. Kubo is the most frustrating.
Why?
Why are you so provocative?
Because I respect you.
I wanted to win this one.
Kubo's wall is high.
Kubo can make noise with his eyes.
That's right.
It's all about the eyes.
Let's continue.
KAION SATO
I've never lost a three-letter shiritori game.
I've never lost a three-character shiritori game.
Hee...
I'll even say I've never lost.
The reason why I'm so strong is...
There's a guy who plays three-character shiritori every time we play right-handed.
That's how I've been trained.
I win every time.
I thought, "I can make this my speciality.
That's when you realized how strong he was?
That's when I realized
I'm really good at three-letter word game.
Shall we? Mr. Sato.
I failed last time.
Let's start with the members.
You want to play with the members?
Those who say they're good at three-letter shiritori.
Here we go.
Okay, let's go.
Let's go.
Let's have him come out then.
So, the champion, Sato, and the persistent Seimiya are going to have a three-character shiritori showdown.
Himemaru-san, what is it?
Let's see... "A" for candy.
Why are you starting with two letters?
Don't start with three letters
Ame no a
Shall we start with "seimya"?
Let's start with Seimiya.
Three-letter word shiritori!
Crackle, crackle, crackle
Ice Watermelon
Kaori Apple
Gorillo Bugle
Pants Stacking blocks
Fox Mouse
Worms Zuko
Gogokkun!
He's so strong!
Yay!
But Seimi was surprisingly strong.
He was strong!
Let's get some more!
Let's go with Kubo!
Kubo's strong, because he's smart at times like this.
Kubo has won many champions.
He just took all of them.
I'll get them all.
All right, let's get to it.
Eye
Eye of eye
From the eyes
I'll start with the eyes.
I'll start from the eyes... yay start!
eye from eye
Map
Pool
Ruby
Dolphin
Kappa
Pants
Building blocks
Keys
Choo-choo!
That's awesome.
Not even close.
Is that thing strong? It's strong.
I'm sure of it.
Shall we go to Ikeda?
He's smart. He knows the language.
Can you stop the No. 1 champion of the achievement test?
Subject: Nogizaka no no
Start the 3-letter word sheet!
Nogizaka no no
Ruby
India
Germany
bricks
fox
mouse
earthworm
cricket
Aah!
Wow!
Amazing!
He's so strong!
You know, you had a pretty tricky attack.
India, and they came back with Germany.
That's great!
Cool!
Then he bows out the real brains
I'm going to give up Sato.
Is that good?
Bugle.
Papa's
He couldn't do anything and easily lost the game
Crying
Shut up, shut up, shut up!
He also defeated the three Shiritori boastful players who ran for
in the blink of an eye.
Oh no, oh no, oh no!
If I do this, well, I'll just have to go!
Come on!
It's not two words, it's three!
Three letters! Come on!
I'm not even good at 3-letter Shiritori to begin with.
But I haven't even tried it yet, and the last time I tried it, I ended up with 2 letters.
I don't know what to do.
Number 3.
Will 2 miracles happen if I do it?
First, I'll play rock-paper-scissors-paper.
All right! First move! First!
Sakayakun, give me a subject!
Okay, Bananaman's Ba!
I'm from Ba!
Let's go! All right, let's begin!
Banana!
Nazuna!
Nappa!
Panda!
Dango!
Gorilla!
Rakiyo!
Yeah!
No, I was trying not to go to regulation.
Oh, no!
Can I say that?
Of course you can.
I'm so happy!
That's great.
Good luck.
I'm gonna win.
You know, if you're going to go into the regs, you might as well say the regs.
That's good. That's good. That's good.
Yeah, that's right.
Okay. - Okay.
What?
You scared me.
Rock, paper, scissors!
I lost.
Tamura, give me a subject.
Okappa no O
3 letter progress
Start
Sushi
Shizuku
medicine
apple
leaf
panda
dice
watermelon
crow
Silver grass
foxes
Rat
Sewing machine.
What?
What? What?
Strong.
Not strong.
So there's some kind of routine?
No, I don't.
Really, for example, if you say "meh" somehow...
I think of "meh" when I'm running.
Amazing.
This time.
I'll get the good ones to do it somewhere else.
Okay.
What about now?
That was...
Why don't you hold some kind of competition?
At Saitama Super Arena?
Something like that.
That's it!
Details of the bonus included in the limited first edition of the 35th single have been determined.
Second round of selection for Yamashita's graduation concert has started.
Second round of selection for Yamashita's graduation concert has begun.
The second selection for Yamashita's graduation concert has begun.
Second round of selection for Yamashita's graduation concert has started!
Hello everyone!
This is Haruka Kuromi from Nogizaka46.
This year again, I'm going to do a new baseball imitation.
This year, I would like to do more baseball imitations.
I've been thinking of doing more baseball imitations.
Well, not only the players but also the members.
I'm mostly on the side of being imitated.
But I would like to be a mimic someday.
I would like to be a mimic someday.
Please subscribe and rate my channel!
This is Haruka Kuromi.